Oh, it's over.
It's over.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Makeup is over.
Osaka, Greenpearl.
Look at her hair style.
Isn't it rare?
She stepped on something.
Cute.
She is like a dumpling.
I did my best.
Cute.
I like the color of the mask.
I'm the second.
I'm the tenth.
Let's go.
You are black.
You are completely black.
I'm really black.
I'm sorry.
Have you had lunch?
It smells good.
It's delicious.
There are many things.
I'm full.
Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
We're at the Tokyo Dome.
We're not in the frame.
Where are we?
We're in Osaka.
We're at the NERV Park Hall.
It's our first day of the hall tour.
It's a big hall tour.
It's huge.
We've been working hard to make this
hall popular.
We're doing our best.
We're almost half the audience.
Thank you.
We're wearing makeup.
You look cute.
Your hair is a little...
Your side hair is fresh.
It's cute.
Can I say that you have a new look?
I think so.
My new look is a school uniform.
I tried the hairstyle I used to do when
I was a student.
I used to wear side hair.
I think it was 7 years ago.
I'm still in my fourth year.
I was in my senior year.
I'm in my senior year.
I'm still wearing my uniform.
I saw you wearing a school uniform.
I made a mistake the other day.
I made a mistake.
I'm still wearing it.
She said she looks 18 years old.
Oh, Ojiuri.
She's going to cosplay soon.
I'm going to cosplay.
I'm going to the school reunion.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
I was wearing a school uniform.
I was told I was cute.
She is cute.
I was wearing a school uniform.
I was told I was cute.
I'm wearing a school uniform.
Do I look different?
Yes, you do.
You look cute.
This is a ear cuff I got as a
graduation gift.
I was going to take a picture.
I was afraid of being photographed.
I didn't wear it when I came here.
I'm afraid of being photographed.
I'm going to wear it.
I don't like wearing a mask.
I know.
I'm afraid of it.
I was on the train.
I was running.
I wasn't running.
When I was running,
I saw a train in the middle of the
platform.
I was worried.
I was on the train.
You should be careful about the sound.
I know.
I was worried.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go to the afternoon class.
We have something special.
I'm going to watch a play.
What do you think?
I'm hungry.
We've already eaten.
We ate a lot.
We ate for 6 hours.
What did we eat?
Around 5.
We ate rice balls.
Bye bye.
We'll do our best.
Please subscribe to this channel.
This is the last one.
Breathe in.
Open your mouth and look to the side.
Look to the front.
Look to the other side.
She is in a rough mood.
She is in a bad mood.
Please give me a hug.
I'm going to do it.
Stay here.
Look.
What?
I'm so happy!
It's my first time!
It's warm.
It's warm!
Yay!
There are other flavors, right?
I did it!
There are two flavors, salt and sauce.
I'm a salt lover.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm done with my makeup!
Ta-da!
This is a mask.
This is a mask for my heart.
I'll do my best!
Bye-bye!
I'm going to get my make-up fixed.
Osaka's tart cookie!
A-yan!
I can't focus on it.
I got it!
A-yan!
It's A-yan!
One more time!
I got it!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!
I don't want to be used here.
I can't use this.
I'll take it off.
This is a cut.
Cut.
I'll be used in an unedited scene.
At the end of the year.
I'll be used in an edited scene.
Getting ready.?
Thank you for watching.
Camera, yaho!
Yaho!
We have something to say today.
That's right.
Kanami-san, what is it?
We are...
What is it?
We are going to join the Tamagawa
Police Station, the police station of
the city for the national transportation
safety movement.
Yay!
I want to do it for a day.
I'm so happy.
It's our first time.
It's amazing.
The actual performance is on March
25th.
We will wear uniforms.
I'm looking forward to it.
We will broadcast on YouTube from 5
p.m.
Please watch it.
We will do our best.
The live will start in about 30
minutes.
Let's do our best.
Bye bye.
You can relax by turning the switch.
Otherwise you can't walk.
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere.
I wonder if it's cold to get wet
somewhere again.
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere.
I want to share my feelings with you.
Let's go anywhere.
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
Drawing a fragment of the future on the
canvas of my damaged heart
It will guide me
Now I can say the reason for my tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops is ringing
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops is ringing
I wear a rainbow dress